Ivan Zolin

Software developer, Data Scientist

I have 8 months of commercial work as a software developer, data analyst and developer of machine learning methods. In particular, I have experience working in startups, in which I worked as an NLP developer, a Full stack developer, and a Tech Lead. I am proficient in basic mathematical sciences, Algorithms and Data structures, as well as programming languages: Python, C/C++, JavaScript.

zolin5269@gmail.com

Saint-Petersburg, Russia

github.com/IMZolin

+79069363300

in linkedin.com/in/ivan-zolin

WORK EXPERIENCE

Laboratory technician

Laboratory of Molecular Neurodegeneration at SPbSTU

07/2023 - Pres06ent Saint-Petersburg, Russia Research and development in the fields of immuno- and biotechnology, gene therapy.

Tasks

- Development of web interface for interacting with the API of PSF(methods to improve three-dimensional images from confocal microscopy using neural networks) applications.
- Development of automatic marking of spheres in the image to obtain an averaged sphere

Contact: Ekaterina Pchitskaya - katrin.pchitskaya@gmail.com

Tech Lead, Software developer Partner Finder

02/2023 - 06/2023 Saint-Petersburg, Russia Startup

Tasks

- Creating a search engine for business offers(sklearn, nltk).
 Merge with recommendations based on user information.
- Scraping the site getting test data for training (ads and users) in json.
- Development of the Ads component, working with the profile page(editor) on the frontend.

Contact: Egor Marin - egor.marin2017@yandex.ru

Fullstack developer

Interactiver

11/2022 - 12/2022 Saint-Petersburg, Russia

Builder for creating interactive educational tasks. LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/company/interactiver/

Tasks

- Make upload files (the current HTML page) to create personalized jobs based on them.
- Learn about deploying the app on Heroku

Contact: Viktor Katsman - vikto9494@gmail.com

EDUCATION

Bachelor's Degree in Applied Mathematics and Computer Science

Peter the Great St. Petersburg Polytechnic University (SPbSTU)

08/2020 - Pres06ent Saint-Petersburg, Russia

SKILLS



PERSONAL PROJECTS

Web service for constructing PSF data of confocal microscopes with automatic ML segmentation of "spheres" in the image (04/2023 - Pres06ent)

- Tools: Computer Vision, ML, REST API, Python, Django, JavaScript, ReactJS, Docker, Redis, Nginx, Celery, Flower.
- The technology has received approval from SPbSTU for development funding.
- Task 1: Develop a web interface for interacting with the backend of PSF applications.
- Task 2: Implement automatic marking of spheres in the image to obtain an averaged sphere (in the process of Bead extraction)

Course work "Maximization raft area of a given shape when the river turns the river by 90 degrees" (04/2023 - 05/2023)

- Tools: Python, pygame, numpy, LaTEX.
- The problem of finding the maximum area of the raft of a given shape, at which it is possible to pass the river bend in 90 degress.
- The shape of the raft: a rectangle with two equal isosceles triangles on two opposite sides.

ToDo List telegram Bot (02/2023 - 04/2023)

- Tools: Python, aiogram, pewee, SQL, PostgreSQL, Docker.
- GitHub: https://github.com/IMZolin/Todolist-Telegram-bot
- Telegram bot, able to create, edit, delete, view to-do tasks, view completed tasks. The task consists of a description, date, time, frequency, attachments (files).

CERTIFICATES

Java. Basic course (08/2022 - 09/2022)

https://stepik.org/cert/1659594

Development of Android applications on Kotlin (09/2022 - 10/2022)

https://stepik.org/cert/1728735

LANGUAGES

Russian Native or Bilingual Proficiency English

Limited Working Proficiency